goshop.com.my 2009-04-10

# GoShop - Colour My Life

|   
  
---  
  
|     
---  
  
MERCURE KOTA KINABALU  
| November 10, 08 | 03:35pm |

Mercure, hospitality know-how that makes every stay unique.

* * *

SenQ® OPENS AT 1BORNEO  
| June 17, 08 | 02:35pm |

SenQ's Grand Opening at 1Borneo Hypermall, Kota Kinabalu.

* * *

|   
  
---  

|   
---  
Welcome to goshop.com.my's privacy policy. This privacy policy sets out how we utilize and protect any information that you provide us when you use this website. 

We are committed to ensure that your privacy is protected. Should we ask you to provide any information by which you can be identified when using this website, then you can be assured that it will only be used in accordance with this privacy statement.   
  
Your Privacy   
By using the goshop.com.my, you agree to the terms and conditions of the User Agreement, including this Privacy Policy, and you consent to goshop.com.my privacy practices. This includes the use and disclosure of any personal information you have shared with us and its transfer to and storage on our servers.   
Information Collection   
You can browse goshop.com.my without telling us who you are or revealing any personal information about yourself. Certain features and services on goshop.com.my require that you register and supply some information that allows us to identify you. We collect some information automatically from your computer while you browse our sites, such as where you go on goshop.com.my and what you do there. We collect your IP address, computer and connection information, browser type and version, operating system and platform, the URLs you come from and go to next, and a cookie number. 

When you register in goshop.com.my, we collect and store your e-mail address and a password. You can also choose to provide the following personal information: 

  * Member/Company profile information, including first and last name, member name and location
  * Fulfillment information, including mailing address and phone or fax number
  * Other information that allows us to personalize your goshop.com.my experience-for example, your filter and profile preferences and the items on your Wish List

We may get additional information from or about you in other ways not specifically described here. For example, you might contact customer support or respond to a survey, or we might get a third-party complaint about you.   
Collaboration Services   
goshop.com.my works with shopping malls listed inside goshop.com.my to provide shopping information and guide to users. You will know you are on a shopping mall website when the shopping mall's logo appears at the top of the page. When you visit a certain shopping mall website, you are subject to that website's privacy policy. goshop.com.my does not receive any personal information about you from that website operator.   
Use of Information   
We use the information we collect to: 

  * operate goshop.com.my
  * provide you with information and services you request
  * customize your experience on goshop.com.my
  * communicate with you about your needs, service updates and other administrative issues
  * send our Editorial team members targeted marketing and promotional offers, based on their communications preferences
  * measure and improve our sites and services
  * resolve disputes, address complaints and troubleshoot technical problems
  * analyze site and user behavior and prepare aggregated reports

Sharing and Disclosure   
Other Digital Heritage Companies. We may share information with our parent company, subsidiaries, joint ventures or other companies under common control, where it may be used to provide joint services or for purposes such as internal statistics, strategic decision-making, customer reviews, identifying customer trends, customer verification, fraud prevention and security. 

Service Providers. We may share your information with service providers under contract who help with our business operations (such as maintaining goshop.com.my and providing related services). 

Special Offers. On goshop.com.my, you may have opportunities to express interest in or register for third-party products and services. If you do, we will provide information about you to the third party to implement your request. 

Feedback. We may use survey results for our internal development and market research and share the results with our affiliates, consultants, vendors and service providers. 

Other Disclosures. We may disclose information when permitted by law or under the good-faith belief that such disclosure is necessary under applicable law; to comply with legal process served on goshop.com.my; to protect the property or interests of goshop.com.my, its agents and employees; or to protect personal safety or the public.   
  
Public Content   
Some portions of goshop.com.my allow you to contribute ratings, comments, reviews and other content to the site and to the merchant via email. We may use the public content to develop aggregate ratings, personalize site views and market products. We may use your public content to personalize site views and identify or feature popular members. For example, we may provide giveaways to the best or most popular reviews and contributors. While we don't expect to transfer the complete review rating and web of trust database to others (except as discussed in this policy), we use the database throughout our network and to generate results for others.   
E-mail Communications   
Choice/Opt-Out. At any time, you have the ability to opt out of receiving marketing communications from goshop.com.my, but you may not opt out of administrative emails (for example, emails about your information) while you are a member of the goshop.com.my. You can opt out by either changing your e-mail preferences or using the link provided at the bottom of each email message. 

Email Tools. If you send emails to a recipient through our site, they will receive your email address and any personal message you include. Although we do not retain in any easily retrievable way the addresses you email, these emails are not private communications. You may not use our email tools to send spam or content that violates the User Agreement. 

Anti-Spam Policy. goshop.com.my does not tolerate spam. We do not send emails to anyone without permission, and we do not sell or rent email addresses to any unauthorized third party. This does not mean that we can prevent spam from happening on the Internet. If you believe that you have received an unsolicited email from us, please contact us and we will investigate.   
  
Cookies and Web Beacons   
goshop.com.my's Cookies. goshop.com.my, and other members of our corporate family who provide us with joint services, will sometimes place anonymous cookies or web beacons on your computer when you visit our sites or our co-branded sites. We use these cookies and web beacons to recognize returning users, measure traffic and activity on the sites, monitor and improve our services and protect against fraud. 

You can block cookies by changing the settings on your browser (contact your ISP for help), but doing so may prevent us from delivering certain services to you. Your browser must be set to accept cookies in order to access the goshop.com.my Network as a registered member. 

Our Advertisers's Cookies. We use the services of third-party advertising companies, who may place cookies that allow them to collect from you and use anonymous information about your visits to goshop.com.my.   
  
Accessing, Reviewing and Changing Your Personal Information   
As a registered member, you can review and change your personal information by accessing your goshop.com.my Account Information. You should promptly update your personal information if it changes or becomes inaccurate. You can close your goshop.com.my account by contacting ust. We may retain some information from closed accounts so that we can comply with law, prevent fraud, assist with investigations, resolve disputes, analyze or troubleshoot programs, enforce our User Agreement and take other actions otherwise permitted by law. If your account or membership is terminated or suspended, we may maintain some information to prevent re-registration.   
Links to Other Sites   
goshop.com.my contains links to other websites. goshop.com.my is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of these sites. If you have concerns about how other websites collect and use information about you, make sure to read that site's own privacy policy.   
Security   
goshop.com.my uses physical, electronic and administrative safeguards, including advanced firewall and password protection for our databases, designed to protect the security of information. We restrict access to your personal information to employees that need to know that information in order to operate, develop or improve our services. However, as you probably know, third parties may unlawfully intercept or access transmissions or private communications. Therefore, although we work very hard to protect your privacy, we do not promise, and you should not expect, that your personal information or private communications will always remain private.   
General   
We may change this policy from time to time, and we will post the amended terms on goshop.com.my. All amended terms will take effect immediately for new users, and 30 days after they are posted for existing users. 

If you have any questions about this privacy policy or the practices of goshop.com.my, you may e-mail us at info@goshop.com.my.
